{
    "subject": "resource/Fish_Tank_(film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:English-language_films",
    "human_readable": "The subject of Fish Tank (film) is Category:English-language films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.976962685585022,
            "question": "Is Fish Tank an English-language film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9084533452987671,
            "question": "Are there any other categories that the film Fish Tank might belong to besides English-language films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8956612944602966,
            "question": "What language is the film Fish Tank?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8452144265174866,
            "question": "Can Fish Tank be categorized as a foreign language film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7974274754524231,
            "question": "To which category does the film Fish Tank belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7419764995574951,
            "question": "What type of films are considered English-language films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.564910888671875,
            "question": "What are some characteristics of English-language films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5440788269042969,
            "question": "What is the significance of a film's language and category?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4747348725795746,
            "question": "Are there any famous examples of English-language films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46879759430885315,
            "question": "Besides language, what other factors contribute to a film's category?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of Fish Tank (film) is Category:English-language films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6834_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous examples of English-language films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6834_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of a film's language and category?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6834_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some characteristics of English-language films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6834_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6834_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6834_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6834_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6834_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6834_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6834_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6834_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6834_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6834_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6834_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n**Explanation:**\n\nThe provided documents consistently refer to \"Fish Tank\" as a British film. This strongly suggests that it falls under the category of English-language films.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the documents, \"Fish Tank\" is indeed a British drama film directed by Andrea Arnold. This information supports the triple that the subject of Fish Tank (film) is Category:British films."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the film \"Fish Tank,\" which includes details that it is a British drama and part of the English-language film category, thus supporting the triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}